I'm the moon
Full moon night, on the loose
Zalabim zalabam zalaboom
I shine so bright in the gloom
I'm the moon, I'm the moon, I'm the moon
Fog thickens
Night vision
Where we gonna end up is unwritten
Grave digger
Go figure
But if you're killing my mood
Good riddance
Ice in my veins
You're gonna need to keep up with the pace
Even faster, aim higher
When you, when you, when you at the crack of dawn
You keep on raving on
You keep on raving on uh
Lighting up the darkest night
Here comes the real one
Set the world on fire
(Baby do you see me now)
Mirror, mirror
Say it, you already know
In your heart, leave a mark
I'm the moon
Full moon night, on the loose
Zalabim zalabam zalaboom
I'm the queen of the tide and the youth
I'm the moon, I'm the moon, I'm the moon
I'm the moon
Full moon night, on the loose
Zalabim zalabam zalaboom
I'm the queen of the tide and the youth
I'm the moon, I'm the moon, I'm the moon
Charismatic, energetic
It's a habit
Oh she stuntin', she stuntin'
I'm in a spaceship coupe
We 'bout to take off
Leave 'em in the dust
Yeah see you later
Outta this world
I'm off the radar
You wish on a star that you had these bars
I whoosh
Gettin' that ah
When we go strut in like woah
Setting on hot
That's what we got
That's how we baking that dough
Lock and we load
Shoot for the stars
We in the sky
Raising the bar
Eyes on the prize
Shining my light
Ready get set
S.O.S
When I flex
Lighting up the darkest night
Here comes the real one
Set the world on fire
(Baby do you see me now)
Mirror, mirror
Say it, you already know
In your heart, leave a mark
I'm the moon
Full moon night, on the loose
Zalabim zalabam zalaboom
I'm the queen of the tide and the youth
I'm the moon, I'm the moon, I'm the moon
Zalabim zalabam zalaboom